Okorafor Chidinma Christiana

Lagos, Nigeria | okoraforchidinma12@gmail.com | 08165381950

Profile

I have 3 years working experience as a customer service and technical support engineer for SKF bearings and M365 applications. I am competent in troubleshooting and resolving complex technical issues related to Office 365 products and bearings.

I also have the basic knowledge of HTML, CSS and Javascript for frontend development. Additionally, I am familiar with version control systems like Git which ensures efficient and organized development of codes.

Education

B.Eng. Electronic Engineering - University of Nigeria, Nsukka	2014-2020
Certification	
SKF Distributor College—SKF	2020-2023
Google Cloud – Coursera	2020
Fundamentals of Project Management—Coursera	2020
Fundamentals of Microsoft Office – New Horizon	2017

Technical Skills

- Html, CSS, JavaScript, Git, ReactJs
- Microsoft Office 365, Exchange Online, SharePoint Online, OneDrive for Business, Teams, PowerShell, Active Directory, DNS
- Agile and Scrum Methodologies
- ClickUp

Soft Skills

- Process Documentation
- Vendor Relationship Management
- Strategic Planning and Analysis
- Self-driven to provide a timely solution
- Public Speaking
- Exceptional Verbal and Written Communication Skills

My Passion Project Links

https://dymacode.github.io/learning-portfolio/ https://dymacode.github.io/web-dev/ https://dymacode.github.io/codebase/ https://dymacode.github.io/my-project/ https://dymacode.github.io/Dog-slide/

Work History

Technical Support Engineer- Tek Experts Nigeria

07/2023-12/2023

- I Provide technical support to clients via phone and email resolving issues promptly and ensuring customer satisfaction.
- Diagnose software problems, troubleshooting technical issues related to Microsoft 365 applications who uses these products in the NOAM region.
- Collaborate with the development team to escalate and resolve complex technical issues, contributing to product improvement.
- Document support processes and created knowledge base articles for common issues, reducing resolution time.

Customer Service – FirstAdvancetek Solutions Limited, Lagos

09/2020-06/2023

- Provided Technical Support for SKF bearings, lubricants, maintenance tools etc. to customers with the goal of keeping customers satisfied.
- Processed documentation for tracking the progress of SKF products and completed 93% on-time delivery.
- I conducted initial Product analysis for companies to determine their needs.
- Developed lasting customer relationships through promos and discounts for loyalty.
- Implemented product changes and recommendations for customers.

Information Technology Intern – Alpha Mead Group, Lagos

06/2017 – 11/2017

- I installed and configured computer hardware, software, systems, networks, printer, and scanners and set up accounts for new users.
- I provided end-to-end technical support for M365 applications and services, including Exchange Online, SharePoint Online, OneDrive for Business, Teams.
- Troubleshoot and resolve complex technical issues related to M365 services, including user management, email routing, calendar sharing, site collection configuration, and data loss prevention.
- Collaborated with team members to deliver technical solutions and training materials to staff on using the Softphone.
- Administered and configured M365 environments, including user management, licensing, security, and compliance.
- Providing technical support across the company to resolve technical issues and improve M365 service delivery (this may be in person or over the phone).
- Documented inquiries and solutions are taken in resolving technical issues.